Come with me on a study crawl. In case
you haven't heard, a study crawl is like
a bar crawl, but instead of hopping
around to different bars and having fun,
you hop around to different study spots
to stay motivated. My first location,
the library. For today's studying, I
packed my notebook, pens, [music]
flashcards, and my Dell XPS 13, which is
$599 for students right now. Okay, first
things first. I have a couple of
lectures to catch up on, so I'm going to
watch those on 2x speed while taking
some notes.
That actually took way less time than I
expected. Now I need to submit a
proposal for my computer vision final
project.
Proposal submitted, but I'm literally
[music] starving. So I think it's time
for our next stop.
I just grabbed some food and now I'm
going to revise my [music] 15page final
paper for my writing seminar.
Also, [music]
this is exactly why I love bringing this
laptop everywhere with me. I've
literally been studying for hours.
[music] And look how much battery I
still have left.
We are all [music] done with revisions.
And for my final stop of the day, I'm
going to head to the law school.
Something about studying here just makes
me feel smarter. I have a research
presentation coming up that's worth a
[music] big part of my grades. So, I
need to finish putting together my
slideshow.
I love that this laptop has a touchcreen
because it's like having a tablet and a
computer in one. Plus, it's powered by
the series 3 Intel Cool processor.
Finally, I just need to respond to a few
[music] emails.
And with that, today's study cruel
[music] is officially complete. See you
guys next time.